<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">Dubai Dial</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="loading">Loading. Please Wait..</string>
    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="version">DD V.10</string>
    <string name="enter_all_details">Please enter all details</string>
    <string name="invalid_pass">Password does not match.Please re-enter valid password</string>
    <string name="logical_error">Unable to connect dubai dail at this moment.Please try again.</string>
    <string name="blankSearhString">Please enter some text to search or select any category.</string>
    <string name="fetch_cityname">Fetching City Names.</string>
    <string name="guest_user">Please Register. Guest user do not have access to for this.</string>
    <string name="forget_pass_text">Enter your email address below and we\&amp;amp;apos;ll send a special reset password link to your inbox.</string>
    <string name="comment">"some thing abt this hotel is good that i have mentioned in this coment please chek this."</string>
    <string name="any_text">
<![CDATA[<font color=#000000>Not a registered user yet? <font color=#0000ff>Sign up now!

]]>
    </string>
    <string name="app_id">337661936386046</string>
    <string name="eula">TERMS OF USE FOR SEARCH SERVICES SEARCH ENGINE DUBAI DIAL &amp;amp;

Privacy Policy:

TERMS OF USE FOR SEARCH SERVICES/SEARCH ENGINE/DUBAI DIAL:

YOUR ACCEPTANCE OF THIS AGREEMENT: This is an agreement between you ("you", 

“your" "caller" or "user") and M/s. Infinite Leads FZ-LLC. ("Infinite leads " "we," or "our") that 

governs your use of the search, booking services or any other services offered by M/s. Infinite Leads 

FZ-LLC through its website www.dubaidial.com ("Website"), telephone search, SMS, WAP, mobile 

application or any other medium (collectively "Platforms" ). When you access, use or book any orders 

using any of the Platforms, you agree to be bound by these Terms and Conditions ("Terms").

1. Definitions &amp;amp; Interpretations

"Agreement" is for the purposes of placing an order of goods through its advertiser registered/listed with 

M/s. Infinite Leads FZ- LLC as described in this agreement. All the orders/enquiries placed by you 

through its website www.dubaidial.com ("Website"), telephone search, SMS, WAP, mobile application 

or any other medium, shall be forwarded by M/s Infinite Leads FZ-LLC to the advertisers listed with us, 

for further processing of your orders.

"Goods" means Goods described in an Order form.

"Intellectual Property Rights" Includes all rights in respect of copyright, trademarks, patents, designs, 

protection of confidential information and circuit layouts, whether arising under statute or otherwise 

registered under Trade Mark Act of U.A.E, As per Patent Laws and Copy Right Act of U.A.E.

"Order" means an enquiries/ booking request placed by you through M/s. Infinite Leads FZ-LLC which 

will in turn will be forwarded to respective Advertiser listed with us via website.

"Product List" means the list of Goods displayed on the www.dubaidial.com-DD ("Website") as 

amended from time to time.

2. Applicability 

The terms of use will be applicable between you and M/s Infinite Leads FZ- LLC once you have placed 

the order for goods as described in this agreement.

3. Placement of Order

You have the option of placing the order by calling to M/s Infinite Leads FZ- LLC Call Centre Number 

and/or by using the booking facility provided on the web, wap , mobile application or by any other means 

as introduced by Infinite Leads FZ LLCC from time to time.

4. Responsibilities

M/s Infinite Leads FZ - LLC does not sell or claim to sell any liquor or any other product online by 

itself.

M/s Infinite Leads FZ- LLC collects customer orders and forwards them to the advertiser which may or 

may not choose to complete the order.

M/s Infinite Leads FZ-LLC is also not responsible for the Quality of any food or other products ordered 

from the website.

To order goods from M/s Infinite Leads FZ -LLC platforms you must be of legal age as specified by 

the appropriate authority and/or as defined in this agreement. Kindly note that persons residing in UAE 

(under 25 years of age or any other age limit/or any other restrictions specified by the appropriate 

authorities) are not permitted to place orders for alcohol, its related products, goods and or any other 

specified goods by the appropriate authority. M/s Infinite Leads FZ-LLC hereby confirms that they shall 

not be responsible for orders relating to Liquor or any other related products and its delivery.

4. Order Completion

You must complete or give requisite details for completing an order form for the purposes of booking 

your order. You warrant that all information and data provided by you in the order form is accurate, 

complete and up to date. If you are placing an order through phone then in that event your order is 

deemed to be completed once the details are filled by the Executive working/representing M/s. Infinite 

Leads FZ-LLC and in case you are placing an online order through website, it is deemed to be complete, 

once the details are filled online in the order form.

5. Delivery

You hereby confirm all products/services are subject to availability and you acknowledge the fact 

that Booking of Orders are taken/booked by M/s Infinite Leads FZ-LLC but the goods/products are 

delivered by advertiser listed with M/s. Infinite Leads FZ-LLC.

No medicine would be delivered by the vendor/ chemist without the valid medical prescription issued by 

the medical practitioner 

6. Miscalculation of Charges/Fees

If the calculation of the fee/charges is insufficient to cover the actual cost of goods which is paid by 

the advertiser to its wholesaler/supplier, then Advertiser is not obligated to fulfill your order. Where 

Advertiser chooses not to absorb the additional fee, Advertiser will notify you that the calculations are 

different from real costs and offer you the option of paying the difference and going ahead with the order. 

You may choose to proceed and pay the higher delivery fee or cancel the order.

7. Return or Refunds

If at any time You are not satisfied with the quality of the Goods you have purchased, You may contact 

the Customer Care of M/s. Infinite Leads FZ-LLC wherein your complaint will be registered and 

shall be forwarded to the respective Advertiser/Supplier for its resolution or you can directly complaint 

to Advertiser and may claim for a credit, replacement or refund of the purchased, damaged or incorrect 

product. Further, you hereby confirm and agree that the You will not claim or allege anything against 

Infinite Leads FZ LLC in respect of the goods/services which are provided to you by the Advertiser/

Supplier.

8. Pricing

M/s. Infinite Leads FZ-LLC reserves the right to alter prices of goods/services at any time as requested 

by the respected advertiser/Supplier of goods. All prices quoted shall be in AED or USD. All orders are 

subject to availability and confirmation by the advertiser/Supplier of the goods and services.

If any product/services ordered is unavailable or incorrectly priced then the Advertiser shall advise you 

regarding the actual price of the product before delivery or shall recommend a suitable substitute of the 

product.

9. Cancellation and Modification

Cancellation or modification of any bookings made through the website shall be strictly in accordance 

with the Advertisers modification and cancellation policy, including with respect to refund. You may 

directly contact the respective advertiser and/or M/s. Infinite Leads FZ-LLC for processing any requests 

pertaining to cancellation or modification. The cancellation and modification request made by you to M/s. 

Infinite Leads FZ-LLC will be forwarded to respective advertiser for its resolution.

We, M/s. Infinite Leads FZ-LLC reserve the right, in its sole discretion and without any obligation, 

to make improvements to, or correct any error or omissions in, any portion of the Platforms. Wherever 

it deems appropriate, we shall endeavor to update information listed on the Website on a timely and 

accurate basis, but shall not be liable for any inaccuracies.

We, M/s. Infinite Leads FZ-LLC reserve the right to disable links to or from third-party sites to any 

of our Platforms, although we are under no obligation to do so. This right to disable links includes links 

to or from advertisers, sponsors, and content partners that may use our Marks as part of a co-branding 

relationship.

All those sections in the Platforms that invite reader participation will contain views, opinion, suggestion, 

comments and other information provided by the general public, and Infinite Leads will at no point of 

time be responsible for the accuracy or correctness of such information. We M/s. Infinite Leads FZ-
LLC reserves the absolute right to accept/reject information from readers and/or advertisements from 

Advertisers and impose/relax Platforms access rules and regulations for any user(s).

We, M/s. Infinite Leads FZ-LLC also reserves the right to impose/change the access regulations of the 

Platforms, whether in terms of access fee, timings, equipment, access restrictions or otherwise, which 

shall be posted from time to time under these terms and conditions. It is the responsibility of users to refer 

to these terms and conditions each time they use the Platforms.

While every attempt has been made to ascertain the authenticity of the content in the Platforms, M/

s. Infinite Leads FZ-LLC is not liable for any kind of damages, losses or action arising directly or 

indirectly, due to access and/or use of the content in the Platforms including but not limited to any 

decisions based on content in the Platforms resulting in loss of data, revenue, profits, property, infection 

by viruses etc.

10. DISCLAIMERS

10.1 Content disclaimer:

We have no control over and are not responsible for the content of any third-party websites linked to or 

framed within the Website, or any third-party advertisements and We expressly disclaim (and do not 

endorse or verify) the accuracy or reliability of the content on any such third-party websites. Those links 

are provided for your convenience only and may not remain current or be maintained. Website links on 

this Website should not be construed as an endorsement, approval or recommendation by us of the linked 

website or its content. We are not responsible for the content or privacy practices or policies associated 

with linked websites. When viewing a third party website, you should read the terms, conditions and 

privacy statements/policies detailed on that website. Your use of or reliance upon such third-party 

websites is at your own risk.

We derive our information from sources which we believe to be accurate and up to date at the time of 

publication. No information on the Site is intended as, or constitutes, professional advice, and should 

not be relied upon as such. All information provided on the Website is provided in good faith. We do 

not make any representation or warranty that the information provided is timely, reliable, accurate or 

complete; and will not be liable for any claim or loss resulting from any action taken, or reliance made 

by you on any information, material or advice provided on the Website, or for any incorrect information 

provided on the Website. No person should act or refrain from acting in reliance upon the information 

in the Site without seeking suitable prior professional advice or contacting M/s. Infinite Leads FZ-LLC 

directly.

We M/s. Infinite Leads FZ-LLC reserve the right to change, update or terminate the Website and 

Content or any part of them at any time in our absolute discretion, without notice or liability to you.

All of the data on products and promotions including but not limited to, the prices and the availability of 

any product or service or any feature thereof, is subject to change without notice by the party providing 

the product or promotion. None of the information contained in the Site constitutes a recommendation, 

solicitation or offer by M/s. Infinite Leads FZ-LLC or its affiliates to buy or sell any securities or other 

financial instruments or provide any investment advice or service. You should use discretion while using 

the Platforms.

10.2 Warranty DISCLAIMER

M/s. Infinite Leads FZ-LLC mandates that any provider of goods or services shall be entitled to 

register with www.dubaidial.com-DD ("Website"). Infinite Leads FZ LLC does not examine whether 

the Advertisers are good, reputable or quality sellers of goods / service providers. You must satisfy 

yourself about all relevant aspects prior to booking / availing services. Infinite Leads has agreed to 

deliver the services but has not negotiated or discussed any terms of engagement with any of the 

Advertisers and shall not be liable to you (whether under the UAE law or otherwise) in relation to 

the contents of, or use of or otherwise in connection with this website. The user is solely responsible 

for the use of the website while booking, purchasing and availing goods and services from Advertisers 

which shall be at his/her own risk and in any event regardless of cause M/s. Infinite Leads FZ-LLC

shall not be held liable for any indirect, special, incidental, punitive or consequential damages of 

any kind, whether arising under breach of contract, tort (including negligence), strict liability or 

otherwise, and whether based on this agreement or otherwise, even if advised of the possibility of 

such damages.

YOU ASSUME ALL RESPONSIBILITY AND RISK FOR THE USE OF THIS PLATFORMS 

AND THE INTERNET GENERALLY. THE FOREGOING LIMITATIONS SHALL APPLY 

NOTWITHSTANDING ANY FAILURE OF THE ESSENTIAL PURPOSE OF ANY LIMITED 

REMEDY AND TO THE FULLEST EXTENT PERMITTED UNDER APPLICABLE LAW. 

SOME COUNTRIES DO NOT ALLOW THE EXCLUSION OR LIMITATION OF LIABILITY 

OF CONSEQUENTIAL OR INCIDENTAL DAMAGES, SO THE ABOVE EXCLUSIONS MAY 

NOT APPLY TO ALL USERS; IN SUCH COUNTRIES LIABILITY IS LIMITED TO THE 

FULLEST EXTENT PERMITTED BY LAW.

We do not investigate, represent or endorse the accuracy, legality, legitimacy, validity or reliability 

of any products, services, deals, coupons or other promotions or materials, including advice, ratings, 

and recommendations contained on, distributed through, or linked, downloaded or accessed from the 

Platforms.

References that we make to any names, marks, products or services of third parties or hypertext 

links to third party sites or information do not constitute or imply our endorsement, sponsorship or 

recommendation of the third party, of the quality of any product or service, advice, information or 

other materials displayed, purchased, or obtained by you as a result of an advertisement or any other 

information or offer in or in connection with the Platforms.

THE MATERIAL AND THE PLATFORMS USED TO PROVIDE THE MATERIAL (INCLUDING 

THE WEBSITE ) ARE PROVIDED "AS IS" AND "AS AVAILABLE" WITHOUT WARRANTY OF 

ANY KIND, EITHER EXPRESS OR IMPLIED OR STATUTORY, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED 

TO, THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR 

PURPOSE, OR NON-INFRINGEMENT. INFINITE LEADS DISCLAIMS, TO THE FULLEST 

EXTENT PERMITTED UNDER LAW, ANY WARRANTIES REGARDING THE SECURITY, 

RELIABILITY, TIMELINESS, ACCURACY AND PERFORMANCE OF THE PLATFORMS AND 

MATERIALS. INFINITE LEADSDOES NOT WARRANT THAT ANY DEFECTS OR ERRORS 

WILL BE CORRECTED; OR THAT THE CONTENT IS FREE OF VIRUSES OR OTHER HARMFUL 

COMPONENTS.

M/s. INFINITE LEADS FZ LLCC DISCLAIMS ANY AND ALL WARRANTIES TO THE FULLEST 

EXTENT OF THE LAW, INCLUDING ANY WARRANTIES FOR ANY INFORMATION, GOODS, 

OR SERVICES, OBTAINED THROUGH, ADVERTISED OR RECEIVED THROUGH ANY 

LINKS PROVIDED BY OR THROUGH THE PLATFORMS SOME COUNTRIES OR OTHER 

JURISDICTIONS DO NOT ALLOW THE EXCLUSION OF IMPLIED WARRANTIES, SO THE 

ABOVE EXCLUSIONS MAY NOT APPLY TO YOU. YOU MAY ALSO HAVE OTHER RIGHTS 

THAT VARY FROM COUNTRY TO COUNTRY AND JURISDICTION TO JURISDICTION.

10.3 DISCLAIMER for "Infinite Leads FZ LLC GUARANTEE" and "Dubai Dial’s Right"

The "Infinite Leads FZ-LLC Guarantee" and "Dubai Dial’s Right" is a limited assurance offered 

by Infinite Leads FZ-LLC that the name and contact information of the Advertiser and the category 

in which the Advertiser is listed by Dubai Dial, have been verified as existing and correct at the time 

of the Advertiser's application to register with Dubai Dial. Infinite Leads makes no representations or 

warranties, whether express or implied, including but not limited to warranties of the continued existence 

and/or operations of the Advertiser, or the quality, quantity, merchantability or fitness for use of the goods 

or services offered by the Advertiser.

10.4 GENERAL DISCLAIMER:

Users using any of services provided by Infinite Leads FZ-LLC cross the following mediums i.e. 

through internet, www.dubaidial.com -DD Website, Wap, SMS, phone including mobile application 

or any other medium are bound by this additional disclaimer wherein they are cautioned to make proper 

enquiry before they (Users) rely, act upon, make any kind of booking or enter into any transaction (any 

kind or any sort of transaction including but not limited to monetary transaction) with the Advertiser 

listed with Dubai Dial.

All the Users are cautioned that all and any information/products/goods or services of whatsoever nature 

provided or received from the Advertiser/s is taken in good faith, without least suspecting the bonafide 

of the Advertiser/s and Infinite Leads does not confirm, acknowledge, or subscribe to the claims and 

representation made by the Advertiser/s listed with Dubai Dial. Further, Infinite Leads is not responsible 

for any act of Advertiser/s listed at Dubai Dial.

11. Unlawful/Illegal Activity

We reserve the right (at our discretion) to investigate complaints or reported violations of the Terms and 

to take any action we deem appropriate including, but not limited to, reporting any suspected unlawful 

activity to law enforcement officials, regulators, or other third-parties and disclosing any information 

necessary or appropriate to such persons or entities relating to your Registration Data, usage history, 

posted materials, IP addresses and traffic information etc. on our website in accordance with UAE Law 

applicable for the same. 

12. Risks

Any risk associated with the goods passes to you upon delivery of the goods to the delivery address by 

the Advertiser/Supplier listed on the website of M/s. Infinite Leads FZ-LLC.

13. Indemnity

You agree to indemnify M/s. Infinite Leads FZ-LLC and its affiliates, employees, agents and 

representatives, and to hold them harmless from any and all claims and liabilities (including any and all 

attorneys' fees) that may arise from your submissions, and from your unauthorized use of goods obtained 

through Infinite Leads FZ LLCC (via its Advertiser), from your breach of this Policy, or from any such 

acts arising through your use of www.dubaidial.com. These obligations will override any termination 

of the Terms and Conditions of the website.

14. Limitation of liability:

You acknowledge that M/s. Infinite Leads FZ-LLC is provided "as is site" and that Infinite Leads FZ 

LLCC is not making and has not made any warranty or representation as to suitability, merchantability, 

quality of the goods which will be supplied or delivered by its listed advertiser for any particular purpose. 

You agree that in using Dubai Dial, You are not relying on any statement or representation made by 

Infinite Leads FZ LLCC which is not expressly contained in this Agreement.

IN NO EVENT SHALL M/S. INFINITE LEADS FZ-LLC BE LIABLE TO YOU ON ACCOUNT OF 

YOUR BOOKING, USE, MISUSE OR RELIANCE ON THE PLATFORMS FOR ANY DAMAGES 

WHATSOEVER, INCLUDING DIRECT, SPECIAL, PUNITIVE, INDIRECT, CONSEQUENTIAL 

OR INCIDENTAL DAMAGES OR DAMAGES FOR LOSS OF PROFITS, REVENUE, USE, OR 

DATA WHETHER BROUGHT IN WARRANTY, CONTRACT, INTELLECTUAL PROPERTY 

INFRINGEMENT, TORT (INCLUDING NEGLIGENCE) OR OTHER THEORY, EVEN IF 

JUST DIAL ARE AWARE OF OR HAVE BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH 

DAMAGE, ARISING OUT OF OR CONNECTED WITH THE USE (OR INABILITY TO USE) OR 

PERFORMANCE OF THE PLATFORMS, THE MATERIALS OR THE INTERNET GENERALLY, 

OR THE USE (OR INABILITY TO USE), RELIANCE UPON OR PERFORMANCE OF ANY 

MATERIAL CONTAINED IN OR ACCESSED FROM ANY PLATFORMS. JUST DIAL DOES 

NOT ASSUME ANY LEGAL LIABILITY OR RESPONSIBILITY FOR THE ACCURACY, 

COMPLETENESS, OR USEFULNESS OF ANY INFORMATION, APPARATUS, PRODUCT OR 

PROCESS DISCLOSED ON THE PLATFORMS OR OTHER MATERIAL ACCESSIBLE FROM THE 

PLATFORMS.

YOU ASSUME ALL RESPONSIBILITY AND RISK FOR THE USE OF THIS PLATFORMS 

AND THE INTERNET GENERALLY, OR THE USE (OR INABILITY TO USE), RELIANCE 

UPON OR PERFORMANCE OF ANY MATERIAL CONTAINED IN OR ACCESSED FROM 

ANY PLATFORMS. INFINITE LEADS FZ LLC DOES NOT ASSUME ANY LEGAL LIABILITY 

OR RESPONSIBILITY FOR THE ACCURACY, COMPLETENESS, OR USEFULNESS OF ANY 

INFORMATION, APPARATUS, PRODUCT OR PROCESS DISCLOSED ON THE PLATFORMS OR 

OTHER MATERIAL ACCESSIBLE FROM THE PLATFORMS.

15. Changes/Amendments :

We may periodically change the Terms and the Site without notice, and you are responsible for checking 

these Terms periodically for revisions. All amended Terms become effective upon our posting on the Site, 

and any use of the site after such revisions have been posted, signifies your consent to the changes. If 

any such change or modification is unacceptable to you, we suggest that you may refrain from using the 

website. If following any such change or modification, you continue to use the Website or its Contents, 

you shall be deemed to have accepted those changes or modifications.

16. Privacy Policy:

M/s. Infinite Leads FZ-LLC is committed to protecting the privacy and confidentiality of any 

personal information that it may request and receive from its clients, business partners and other users 

of the Website. To read our privacy policy statement regarding such personal information please refer 

PRIVACY POLICY

You hereby confirm and acknowledge that the contact details and other details provided by you in 

connection with any calls or enquiries made by you to M/s. Infinite Leads FZ-LLC shall be used and 

forwarded by Infinite Leads to the respective Advertiser.

17. General/Miscellaneous Instructions

Dubai Dial's listed advertiser/ actual business owners who has processed and delivered your order as per 

your request is solely responsible for quality, delivery and billing of the products. M/s. Infinite Leads 

FZ-LLC only acts as channel between you and the actual business owners/listed advertiser.

We make no representation and give no warranty or undertaking (express or implied) as to the timeliness, 

accuracy, completeness, effectiveness or reliability of the Website or its Content for any particular 

purpose.

We make no representation and give no warranty or undertaking (express or implied) as to the timeliness, 

accuracy, completeness, effectiveness or reliability of the goods supplied/delivered by the Advertiser.

We will not be responsible or liable for any loss, damage, injury or other claim or outcome arising from 

your reliance upon the Website, or the Website's inability to meet your needs.

We make no representation that materials or other content in the Site are appropriate or available for use 

outside UAE. If you choose to access the Site from other locations or being an alien you do it on your 

own initiative and at your own risk.

We will not be responsible for any delay, failure, interruption, or corruption of any data or other 

information transmitted in connection with your use of the Website, which is beyond our control. For 

the avoidance of doubt, we do not accept responsibility for any interference or damage to your computer 

system which may arise in connection with your use of the Website or any linked website.

18. Links to other Websites:

M/s. Infinite Leads FZ-LLC shall not be responsible for any links to other websites which may occur 

while accessing www.dubaidial.com. The links are places on the website for customer convenience and 

user understands and acknowledges by virtue of usage of the website that any access to such sites is 

at user’s own risk. M/s. Infinite Leads FZ-LLC does not control such sites or the information contained 

therein and shall not be responsible for any loss or damages that the user may sustain as a result of the use 

of such websites or accessing the information contained therein.

19. Force Majeure

Infinite Leads and its advertiser will be not be liable for breach of this terms of use to the extent caused 

by or arising from prohibition or restriction by law or regulation or any government, fire, flood, storms, 

weather, strike, lock-out or other labour problems, accident, riots, acts of God or any other events which 

is beyond its control.

20. Arbitration:

In the event a dispute arises between you and M/s. Infinite Leads FZ-LLC as per the terms of use, the 

parties shall attempt to amicably resolve the dispute through mutual discussions. Where the dispute is 

not resolved for a period of 90 days from the date of the dispute, either party can, upon giving a written 

notice to the other party, declare its intention to initiate arbitration proceedings. The arbitration will be 

conducted in English in accordance with the provisions of DIFC Arbitration LAW 2008. The venue for 

the arbitration shall be UAE. The arbitration shall be conducted by a sole arbitrator appointed by M/s. 

Infinite Leads FZ-LLC. The judgment /verdict of the Arbitration Tribunal shall be final and binding on 

the parties. Cost of arbitration shall be in accordance with the Judgment/Order

21. Governing Law and Jurisdiction:

The terms and conditions of search services provided by M/s. Infinite Leads FZ-LLC shall be governed 

and construed in accordance with the UAE Law. 

22. Severance

Each provision of this Agreement (including these Conditions) is severable. Severance does not affect any 

other provisions.

If you have any concern or non-acceptance of the terms and policies mentioned above please do exit 

www.dubaidial.com.

For further queries &amp;amp; assistance, you may mail us on our complaint@dubaidial.com &amp;amp; ask for our 

Customer Support team </string>
    <string name="eula1">This Privacy Policy for www.dubaidial.com-DD ("Website") is to be read, understood and applied 

in connection with the Terms &amp; Conditions which are also exhibited/displayed on this website. 

This Privacy Policy has been formulated to enable users understand how their Privacy is protected 

and upon visiting the website and also for a better understanding of the website and the Company 

objective to provide quality service and output to all Users/Customers. 

Introduction

In the course of registering for and availing various services we provide from time to time through our 

website www.dubaidial.com-DD ("Website"),telephone search, SMS, WAP, Mobile application or 

any other medium in which Dubai Dial may provide services (collectively referred to as "Media"), it is 

important for Infinite Leads FZ-LLC to collect, use and share personal information for which, you 

may be required to give your name, residence address, workplace address, email address, date of birth, 

educational qualifications and similar Personal Information ("Personal Information"). 

Personal Information

The Personal Information is used for general purposes: 

ÿ To customize the content you see, 

ÿ To fulfill your requests for services requested through our website,

ÿ To resolve disputes and collect fees

ÿ To encourage and facilitate smooth and safe usage of the website and related services

ÿ To communicate any promotions/offers to the users

ÿ To obtain customer/user feedback you about our services and to provide updates as and 

when required as the case maybe. 

Unless otherwise stated explicitly, this Policy applies to Personal Information as disclosed on any of the 

Media as abovementioned.

We are committed to protecting the privacy and confidentiality of all Personal Information that you may 

share as a user of Media. In furtherance thereof, we have this policy to demonstrate our good faith.

You acknowledge that you are disclosing Personal Information voluntarily. Prior to the completion of any 

registration process on our website or prior to availing of any services offered on our website if you wish 

not to disclose any Personal Information you may refrain from doing so; however if you dont provide 

information that is requested, it is possible that the registration process would be incomplete and/or you 

would not be able to avail our services.

This policy does not apply to the practices of organizations that we do not own or to people that we do not 

employ or manage.

Disclosure of Information:

Personal Information will be kept confidential and will be used for our research, marketing, and strategic 

client analysis objectives and other internal business purposes only. "Infinite Leads FZ - LLC" does not 

rent, sell, disclose or share personal information about you with other people or nonaffiliated companies 

except to provide products, services, or information you have requested when you are a customer of our 

search services through any of the Media after obtaining your permission wherein you shall be deemed to 

have given your consent for the same , or under the following circumstances:

ÿ For any legal issues in order to establish/exercise our legal rights or defend against any 

legal claims which may arise in future

ÿ To enable investigate, prevent or take necessary legal action against any suspected illegal 

activities, fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, 

violations of Terms and Conditions, or as otherwise required by UAE Law.

"Infinite Leads FZ-LLC" does not provide any personal information to the advertiser when you interact with 

or view an advertisement.

Further, the subscribers / advertisers who are listed with us, may call you, based on the query or enquiry 

that you make with us, enquiring about any

• Product / Service or

• Product / Service of any subscriber / advertiser or

• Product / Service of any particular subscriber / advertiser.

Internet Cookies

Like all other websites, we use cookies to improve the content and the services provided to you while 

you are using our website. Cookies do not contain or capture any personal information but it may capture 

computer identification information.

Most Internet browsers automatically accept cookies, however, you have the option to either accept or stop 

accepting cookies by changing your computer browser settings accordingly. Your decision to refuse cookies 

from www.dubaidial.com-DD will not prevent you from using our website but may limit your option to use 

some of our advanced features

Advertiser Listing

The website of Infinite Leads FZ-LLC contains third party advertisers listed which includes advertisers 

listed with/without their permission. For those advertisers listed without their permission has any objection, 

the available options are to either contact Infinite Leads FZ-LLC or to address the concern in writing to the 

Company within a period of 7 working days and the listing shall be removed within....working days.

Any update or change of records/information of the Agent/Advertiser shall have to communicated to Infinite

Leads FZ-LLC via email and the necessary changes shall take effect within a period of 3 working days.

Payments and Third Party Advertisers

All the payments shall be made to Infinite Leads FZ-LLC by the users via cheques and bank transfer. 

Infinite Leads FZ-LLC shall not be responsible for any payments made by the users to any third party 

advertisers/agents. Our connection with the Advertisers/agents shall be limited to serve or present the ads 

that appear on our website.

Privacy and Security

We give you the ability to edit your account information and preferences at any time, including whether you 

want us to contact you about new services. 

All personal electronic details will be kept private by the “website” except for those that you wish to disclose.

To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before 

granting access or making corrections.

In case of any act which is in violation of the laws of UAE, and/or the terms of use of the Service you forfeit your 

privacy rights over your personal information.

Infinite Leads FZ-LLC takes your security seriously and takes reasonable steps to protect your 

information.

However, no internet transactions or usage can be guaranteed as 100% secure and safe. We shall strive 

to take reasonable efforts to ensure and safeguard the systems comprising our website. The possibility 

of information provided by the users being destroyed/accessed/disclosed due to dysfunction or breach of 

software/firewalls we may employ cannot be ruled out. 

Infinite Leads FZ - LLC shall take all measures to evaluate and implement the latest available software 

technology to minimize unauthorized access and associated risks, however we cannot guarantee the users 

a total risk free technology in our system. 

Secure Storage

Infinite Leads FZ - LLC maintains physical, electronic safeguards to protect personal information in 

accordance with the procedures of UAE Law

If you are our corporate customer, it is possible that we have entered into a contract with you for non-
disclosure of confidential information. This Policy shall not affect such a contract in any manner.

Marketing/Customer Service

If a user has once provided information to Infinite Leads FZ – LLC, he/she may receive emails/telephone 

calls/SMS from the Company or its associated branches in UAE, from time to time which contains 

promotional materials/market research surveys/ news updates. If any user does not intend to receive them, 

they may contact the details listed below:

Infinite Leads FZ-LLZ Customer Care:

Please provide the address

Privacy Policy Updates 

Infinite Leads FZ – LLC reserves the right to update this Private Policy to reflect any changes from time to 

time. In such cases, the latest Privacy Policy supersedes and replaces all the previously posted Privacy 

Policies.

If you have any questions or concerns about the privacy policies please email us 

 at privacy@dubaidial.com.</string>

</resources>